Nana Aba Ackah

nanaabaackah@gmail.com | 647-916-2361 | LinkedIn | Github | Peterborough, ON | she/her

SUMMARY

Budding full stack engineer with a Business & Computer Science degree and 2 years of experience with frontend and backend programming

SKILLS (Years of experience listed after each item.)

Languages: Python 1 | JavaScript 1 | C# 1.5 | HTML 2 | CSS 2 | Java 0.5 | R 1

Databases: MySQL 2

Other: Git 1

EDUCATION

BA Hons Business and Computing Systems,

Sept 2017 - Jan 2022

Trent University, Peterborough, Canada

- Relevant Coursework: Financial Management, Strategic Management, Fund Managerial Accounting,
 Data Structures and Algorithms, Software Design and Modeling
- Co-Curricular: Convocation Usher, Electricity Hackathon(Organizer and Volunteer), Trent International Cultural Assistant, Global Ambassador.

EXPERIENCE

Walmart Canada | Cashier

Aug 2019 - Present

- Responsible for 900 scans per hour when ringing up customers in a timely manner to guarantee high level of customer service
- Ensure positive customer experiences and resolved all customer complaints
- Maintain up-to-date knowledge of store policies regarding payments, returns and exchanges
- Assist floor associates with the restocking of misplaced items and removing any unpurchased merchandise from the register area and restocking it in the appropriate areas

Lala Skin Essentials | Digital Marketing Intern

Jan 2022 - April 2022

- Created various marketing strategies which includes creating various campaigns, posts, and other tools to help boost digital interaction with the company
- Researched and generated campaigns for the African affiliate of Lala Skin Essentials with a curated list
 of 30 potential influencers that could partner with the company to help reach a wider audience outside
 of their Canadian target market

Nana Aba Ackah

 Produced reports to illustrate marketing strategies to be applied and have a standard process of operation

Trent African & Caribbean Students Union | Director of Events

Apr 2019 - May 2020

- Planned and organized 15 events per academic year for the union to increase awareness of African and Caribbean cultures
- Worked with other organizations including the Mayor of Peterborough to organize events to improve the livelihood of African and Caribbean students in Trent University and Peterborough
- With assistance from the Director of Finance, created and managed budget of \$5,000 for all events throughout the year
- Directed a subcommittee to ensure that events organized are planned out appropriately

MTN Ghana | Information Technology Department Intern

Jan 2017 - Mar 2017

- Managed the database by using 50 queries weekly to pull data for inventory purposes.
- Completed data entry tasks and calculations using Microsoft Excel to facilitate incoming data
- Fulfilled training requirements on the network structure used by the company to assess the source of technical issues

Smartline Publishers | Marketing Assistant Intern

Aug 2016 - Dec 2016

- Assisted the marketing team with promotional content of the company's products to push their books to retailers, and increase sales
- Participated in outreach events such as fairs, door to door sales and others to improve public awareness of the company
- Contacted about 100 potential and current clients daily to maintain relationship and address any incoming concerns

SPECIAL PROJECTS

Master Budget Project: Prepared a master budget for a company's fiscal year using Microsoft Excel which included sales budget, schedule of cash receipts, production budget and other useful budgetary constraints

<u>Financial Management Project</u>: Involved researching, analyzing and interpreting financial management information of Randstad Holding including cash flows, ratio analysis, bond valuation, common shares and other corporate financial tools.

<u>Database Management Project</u>: This project involves the use of CRUD (..) functions to manage and create a relational database using MySQL.

<u>Scheduling website:</u> This is a scheduling website which allows users to create accounts, check scheduled meetings, organize meetings where invited users can sign up for the meeting and choose a slot for meeting. This involves the use of PHP, SQL, Javascript, API.